http://www.eccu.org/privacy/index

Giving Online or App
Point of Sale (In-Person)
Merchant Services
Accounting & Invoicing (Autobooks)
Better Rates
From Auto to Personal, ECCU has the loan rates you need.
Members Apply
Investing
Privacy
Online Privacy Policy
As financial service professionals entrusted with sensitive financial information, we recognize the customer’s rights to privacy and remain committed to treating customer information responsibly. We believe protecting your information is as important as safeguarding your money. This Online Privacy Policy explains how we collect, share, use, and protect information when you visit or use any of our online services. At Evangelical Christian Credit Union (ECCU), we pledge to serve our customers efficiently and conveniently while maintaining the security they deserve.
If you have a financial product or service with us, we will use and share any information that we collect from or about you in accordance with our ECCU's Member Privacy Policy.
1. Information We Collect
In the course of doing business, we collect and use various types of information, such as information available from public records, credit reports, as well as information you provide to us, including personal information such as your financial status, employment history, marital status, age, email or mailing address, telephone numbers, and other personal information. We also collect information about your accounts, loans, online applications and forms, and other financial transactions and information where we believe it is reasonably required for ordinary business purposes.
2. How We Use Your Information
We may use the information discussed above in various ways, such as:
Processing applications and transactions;
Verifying your identity in order to allow you online access to your accounts, to conduct online transactions, and to enhance the security of your account and protect your personal information;
Responding to your inquiries;
Complying with applicable law and regulation, other legal process, and law enforcement requirements;
Sending you important information about your account(s), products, and services; and
Performing audits, data analyses, usage trends, and the effectiveness of promotional campaigns in order to evaluate and improve upon our business, products, and services.
3. With Whom ECCU May Share Information
ECCU shares personal information with third parties only as permitted or required by law in connection with the administration, processing, and servicing of account and account-related transactions, in order to perform services for us on your behalf. These services include, but are not limited to, credit reporting agencies, bill payment processors, credit, debit and ATM card processing networks, data processors, check printers, marketing and other companies in order to offer and/or provide financial products and services to you, and in response to legal or regulatory requirements, court orders, and/or other legal processes or investigations.
4. How We Collect and Use Other Information
We may collect and use other information, such as:
Cookies: Cookies are pieces of information stored directly on the device you are using. Cookies we use do not contain or capture unencrypted Personal Information. Cookies allow us to collect information such as browser type, time spent on the Site, pages visited, and language preferences. We use the information for security purposes, to facilitate navigation, to display information more effectively, and to recognize your device to allow your use of our online products and services. We collect statistical information about the usage of the Site in order to continually improve the design and functionality, to monitor responses to our advertisements and content, to understand how account holders and visitors use the Site, and to assist us with resolving questions regarding the Site. We also utilize cookies for advertising purposes. Please see the Advertising section below for more information.
You can refuse to accept these cookies and most devices and browsers offer their own privacy settings for cookies.
You will need to manage your cookie settings for each device and browser you use. However, if you do not accept these cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of the Site and some online products and services. For example, we will not be able to recognize your device and you will need to answer a challenge question each time you log on. You also may not receive tailored advertising or other offers from us that may be relevant to your interests and needs.
IP Address: Your IP Address is a number that is automatically assigned to the device that you are using by your Internet Service Provider (ISP). An IP Address is identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever a user visits the Site, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) that were visited. Collecting IP Addresses is standard practice on the internet and is done automatically by many web sites. We use IP Addresses for purposes such as calculating Site usage levels, helping diagnose server problems, compliance and security, advertising, and administering the Site. Please see the Advertising section below for more information.
5. Advertising
ECCU uses information described in this notice to help advertise our products and services in a variety of ways, such as:
Present tailored ads to you, including:
Banner ads and messages that appear as you sign on or off your online accounts on our Sites or conduct online banking within our Sites;
Email and postal mail; and
On other sites and mobile apps not affiliated with ECCU; and
Analyze the effectiveness of our ads; and
Determine whether you might be interested in new products or services.
6. Protecting Your Information, Confidentiality and Security
To protect Personal Information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with applicable federal and state laws. These measures may include device safeguards and secured files and buildings, as well as oversight of our third-party service providers to ensure information remains confidential and secure. Whenever we ask for personal information on our website, we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL Technology) for transferring data. This technology encrypts or scrambles your account information so it's virtually impossible for anyone other than ECCU to read.
Our employees are informed and trained on their responsibility to protect confidential customer information and are bound by this Online Privacy Policy as well as additional internal policies. We limit employee access to confidential customer information to those employees with a business reason to know such information.
7. Accuracy of Information
Keeping your account information accurate and up to date is very important. If your account information is incomplete, inaccurate, or not current, please use the “Contact” options on our Site: www.eccu.org/contact.
8. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) Disclosure
The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”) restricts the collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information from and about children under the age of 13 on the internet. ECCU does not knowingly solicit data from children, nor do we knowingly market to children. ECCU is, however, committed to complying with COPPA and protecting the online privacy of the children who visit our website and/or use our youth online and mobile services.
We recognize that protecting children’s identities and privacy online is important and that the responsibility to do so rests with both the online industry and with parents. We do not knowingly collect personal information from minors without parental consent.
9. When Information is Collected
Some areas of our website require information, such as your email address or your account, to enable you to perform certain tasks (for example, review your accounts or correspond with us). In these cases, we collect your information, if necessary, to interact with you.
10. Social Media Sites
ECCU may provide experiences on social media platforms including, but not limited to, Facebook®, Twitter®, YouTube®, and LinkedIn®, that enable online sharing and collaboration among users who have registered to use them. Any content you post on official ECCU-managed social media pages, such as pictures, information, opinions, or any Personal Information that you make available to other participants on these social platforms, is subject to the Terms of Use and Privacy Policies of those respective platforms. Please refer to them to better understand your rights and obligations with regard to such content. In addition, please note that when visiting any official ECCU social media pages, you are also subject to ECCU's Privacy Policies and all other applicable guidelines and agreements.
11. Links to Other Sites
We may provide links to other websites. In a few cases, we link to private organizations, with their permission. Once you link to another site, you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site. Please note that since we cannot control information on other Internet sites, we are not responsible for the content on these sites.
12. Updates to this Privacy Policy
This Online Privacy Policy is subject to change. Please review it periodically. If we make changes to the Online Privacy Policy, we will revise the “Last Updated” date at the top of this Policy. Any changes to this Policy will become effective when we post the revised Policy on the Site. Your use of the Site following these changes means that you accept the revised Policy.
ABOUT ECCU PRIVACY
ECCU's Member Privacy Policy
CCPA Privacy Policy
Press 'Enter' to search
×Close
Warning
You are leaving Evangelical Christian Credit Union’s (ECCU) web site. Links accessed from this site are for informational purposes only. ECCU does not endorse the content, products, or services published on linked sites. The site you are about to visit has its own privacy policy and level of security, which may be different than ECCU’s. Please review the site’s policy and security certificate.
To leave eccu.org, click “Continue”. If you would like to go back to the previous page, click the “Return to ECCU” button now.
Return to ECCU
Continue
×Close
IMPORTANT: CREDIT CARD ACCESS
You can now view your rewards balance and redeem cash by logging in to online or mobile banking.
No more separate login to access your rewards and view credit card information.
Return and Log into Online Banking
×Close
REMINDER!
Don't forget to use the promo code "HSLDA" when prompted in the online application to qualify for this offer.
Open My Account
×Close
REMINDER!
Don't forget to use the promo code "DRRATE" when prompted in the online application to qualify for the .50% APY increase offer.
Open My Account
×Close
REMINDER!
Don't forget to use the promo code "HSRATE" when prompted in the online application to qualify for the .50% APY increase offer.
Open My Account
×Close
REMINDER!
Don't forget to use the promo code "RAMSEY" when prompted in the online application to qualify for the $50 offer.
Open My Account
×Close
DON'T FORGET...
...to use your promo code when prompted in the online application to qualify for your special offer.
Open My Account
×Close
DON'T FORGET...
...to use your promo code when prompted in the online application to qualify for your special offer.
Open My Account
×Close
DON'T FORGET...
...to use your promo code when prompted in the online application to qualify for your special offer.
Open My Account
×Close
REMINDER!
Don't forget to use the promo code "CHRATE" when prompted in the online application to qualify for the .50% APY increase offer.
Open My Account
×Close
REMINDER!
Don't forget to use the promo code "CTRATE" when prompted in the online application to qualify for the .50% APY increase offer.
Open My Account
×Close
REMINDER!
Don't forget to use the promo code "RMRATE" when prompted in the online application to qualify for the .50% APY increase offer.
Open My Account
×Close
REMINDER
Thank you for choosing to open an additional account with ECCU. Please note, only the primary account signer is eligible to add a new account.
Add an Account
×Close
ECCU Credit Card Videos...
You are leaving the ECCU website for an overview video about managing credit card transactions, statements, alerts, payments, and more. EZCard is an ECCU banking service partner.
Return to ECCU
Continue
If you are using a screen reader and are having problems viewing this website, please call for assistance at 800-634-3228.
High Contrast Mode
Close
×Close
Budget Management Tool
×Close
Spending Management Tool
×Close
Spending Management Tool
×Close
Transfer Money
×Close
WARNING
You are leaving Evangelical Christian Credit Union’s (ECCU) web site. The site you are about to visit has its own privacy policy and level of security, which may be different than ECCU’s. Please review the site’s policy and security certificate.
To leave eccu.org, click “Continue”. If you would like to go back to the previous page, click the “Return to ECCU” button now.
Return to ECCU
Continue
×Close
WARNING
The website mobile terms, privacy and security policies of ECCU do not apply to the following site or app. Please review the respective terms, privacy and security policies of each site to see how they apply to you. ECCU is not responsible for and does not provide any products, services or content at the following third-party site or app. To proceed, select ‘continue’ below.
To leave eccu.org, click “Continue”. If you would like to go back to the previous page, click the “Return to ECCU” button now.
Return to ECCU
Continue
×Close
WHAT WE BELIEVE
The Bible, consisting of all the books of the Old and New Testaments, is the inspired, only infallible, authoritative Word of God. The Scriptures of the Old and New Testaments are without error or misstatement in their moral and spiritual teaching and record of historical facts. They are without error or defect of any kind.
There is one God, eternally existent in three persons: Father, Son, and Holy Spirit.
We believe in the deity of our Lord Jesus Christ, in his virgin birth, his eternal, personal pre-existence, his sinless life, his miracles, his vicarious and atoning death through his shed blood, his bodily resurrection, his ascension to the right hand of the Father, and his personal return in power and glory.
For the salvation of lost and sinful men, regeneration by the Holy Spirit is absolutely essential.
The present ministry of the Holy Spirit is to indwell and enable the Christian to live a godly life.
Resurrection is of both the saved and the lost; they that are saved unto the resurrection of life and they that are lost unto the resurrection of damnation.
We believe in the spiritual unity of believers in our Lord Jesus Christ.
Return to ECCU
ECCU may collect information from users of our website. To see how this information is used, click here to go to our privacy page. Information we may collect: IP address, browsing history, search history, products and services considered, products and services obtained, geolocation data, and information about your interaction with our website, application or advertisement. If you complete an online form, we may also collect your name, e-mail address, physical address or phone number that you provide to us.
OK
×Close
ATTENTION APPLICANTS
ECCU offers credit cards to existing members. If you would like to become a member, we suggest you apply for one of our checking or savings accounts.
Already a member? To continue and apply for our ECCU credit card, click the “continue” button below and log into your Online Banking.
Return to ECCU
Continue
×Close
ATTENTION APPLICANTS
ECCU offers loans to existing members. If you would like to become a member, we suggest you apply for one of our checking or savings accounts.
Already a member? To continue and get pre-approved for an ECCU loan, click the “continue” button below and log into your Online Banking.
Return to ECCU
Continue
×Close
ECCU | KASASA Checking Accounts
Join ECCU
Open Kasasa Account
ECCU Existing Members Log in to add an account or to convert an existing account, send a secure message.
Online Banking
Return to ECCU
×Close
WARNING
You are leaving Evangelical Christian Credit Union’s (ECCU) web site. The site you are about to visit has its own privacy policy and level of security, which may be different than ECCU’s. Please review the site’s policy and security certificate.
To leave eccu.org, click “Continue”. If you would like to go back to the previous page, click the “Return to ECCU” button now.
Return to ECCU
Continue
